<Product Revision="6" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/0002:0003:0005</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/danfoss/z.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0003" name="ZWProductPage" type="0005">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/932/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPage">http://heating.consumers.danfoss.com/xxTypex/585379.html</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0003" name="Identifier" type="0005">014G0013</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0003" name="FrequencyName" type="0005">CEPT (Europe)</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">Danfoss Living Connect Z Electronic radiator thermostat</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">living connect速 is an Z-Wave controlled electronic radiator thermostat. It is controlled by either a Z-Wave compatible Controller or a central device called Danfoss LinkTM CC. The Danfoss LinkTM CC can also control hydronic and electrical floor heating and on/off switches in a building. living connect速 uses Z-Wave wireless communication technology, is easy to install and is supplied with adapters for all thermostatic valves manufactured by Danfoss and most other radiator valve manufacturers.

living connect速 is battery powered, compact and very easy to operate with only three buttons on the front.

Additionally the temperature can be set wirelessly to a certain setpoint. The device has a scheduler inside that allows to set up to 9 different setpoint for each day of a 7 day week. This means that energy saving is even achieved when the controlling device is offline or not working. Local buttons can always overwrite the scheduled setting. living connect速 features an open-window function, which closes the valve if the temperature in the room is falling dramatically.</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="03 May 2019" revision="5">Initial Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/932/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="03 May 2019" revision="6">Updated Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/967/xml</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
    <MetaDataItem id="0004" name="ZWProductPage" type="0005">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/967/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0004" name="Identifier" type="0005">014G0013</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="0004" name="FrequencyName" type="0005">CEPT (Europe)</MetaDataItem>
  </MetaData>
  <!-- http://www.popp.eu/wp-content/uploads/2016/07/Manual_Thermostat_POPP_en.pdf -->
  <!-- COMMAND_CLASS_BASIC does not respond to requests -->
  <CommandClass action="remove" id="32"/>
  <!-- This thermostat's setpoint descriptions are 0 based -->
  <CommandClass id="67">
    <Compatibility>
      <OverridePrecision>2</OverridePrecision>
      <Base>0</Base>
    </Compatibility>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
