<Product Revision="6" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/0312:241C:B211</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/inovelli/simple_module.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="241C" name="ZWProductPage" type="B211">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/2385/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">Use controller to remove device from network will reset it to factory default.

"Use this procedure only in the event that the network primary controller is missing or otherwise inoperable."
 </MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="241C" name="Identifier" type="B211">NZW37</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">Smart Plug-In Module (2 Channel)</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://Products.Z-WaveAlliance.org/ProductManual/File?folder=&amp;filename=Manuals/2385/51010 NZW37 Manual.pdf</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">Inovelli's Dual Smart Plug-In On/Off Module + Repeater has the ability to turn on and off appliances, lights, and more from anywhere in the world from two different outlets! In addition to the dual smart outlets, the smart plug acts as a Z-Wave signal repeater, which amplifies your Z-Wave signal, growing the capabilities of your network. 

This smart plug is one of the smallest plugs on the market (3.5"x2.5"x1.5") and has two (2) Z-Wave Outlets on the side of the device allowing for easy fit in compact places. You can control each outlet individually (and simultaneously*) with all HUB's that support multi-channel Z-Wave devices. Simplifying lives, one smart home product at a time... that's Inovelli.

*Please see our Amazon or our website for compatible HUB's</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">1. Follow the instructions for your Z-Wave certified controller to include a device to the Z-Wave network.

2. Once the controller is ready to Include your device, press the center button 3-5 times within 3 seconds.

3. Once your controller has confirmed that the device has been included, refresh the Z-Wave network to optimize performance.

4. The device is associated in the same group when it included in setting process. 

Now you can control your Z-Wave device according to groups, scenes, schedules  and automation programmed.

** NOTE: If your product does not include at first, try moving the module closer to the HUB and try again -- you can move to your final location when complete

For setup instructions for your specific HUB (ie: SmartThings, Wink, Vera, etc) please go to: www.inovelli.com/nzw37-setup </MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="241C" name="FrequencyName" type="B211">U.S. / Canada / Mexico</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">1. Follow the instructions for your Z-Wave certified controller to exclude  a device from the Z-Wave network.

2. Once the controller is ready to Exclude your device, press the center button 3-5 times within 3 seconds to exclude it from the network. </MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="02 Jun 2019" revision="2">Initial Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/2352/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="02 Jun 2019" revision="3">Updated Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/2357/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="02 Jun 2019" revision="4">Updated Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/2358/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="02 Jun 2019" revision="5">Updated Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/2379/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="02 Jun 2019" revision="6">Updated Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/2385/xml</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
    <MetaDataItem id="271C" name="ZWProductPage" type="B212">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/2379/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="271C" name="Identifier" type="B212">NZW39</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="271C" name="FrequencyName" type="B212">U.S. / Canada / Mexico</MetaDataItem>
  </MetaData>
  <!-- Configuration Parameters -->
  <CommandClass id="112"></CommandClass>
  <!-- Association Groups -->
  <CommandClass id="133">
    <Associations num_groups="1">
      <Group index="1" label="Lifeline" max_associations="5"/>
    </Associations>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
