<Product Revision="1" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/0063:3030:5250</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/ge/45604.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3030" name="ZWProductPage" type="5250">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/655/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">Outdoor Plug-In On/Off Relay Control, Black</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductSupport">http://www.jascoproducts.com/support/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPage">www.ezzwave.com</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3030" name="FrequencyName" type="5250">U.S. / Canada / Mexico</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">"Transform any home into a smart home with the Jasco Z-Wave Wireless Lighting Control Outdoor Module. The outdoor lighting control enables wireless control of on/off functions for outdoor applications, and is compatible with incandescent, LED, Xenon, Halogen, fluorescent and compact fluorescent bulbs. The weather-resistant housing with a protective outlet cover safeguards the outlet from dirt and debris when not in use. The discreet black color blends in with any outdoor environment. Perfect for decorative or seasonal lighting, fountains and other outdoor plug-in appliances. Take control of your home lighting with Jasco Z-Wave Wireless Lighting Controls!

Z-Wave is the world’s largest ecosystem of interoperable smart home products. Z-Wave lighting controls provide an easy-to-install and affordable system to control lighting and small appliances in your home. Add Jasco Z-Wave lighting controls to a Z-Wave certified gateway to access and control your home from anywhere in the world using your smartphone, tablet or computer as a home automation command center. Never worry if you accidentally left the lights on because you can turn them off remotely or program your lights to go on/off at specific times. Create customized lighting scenes for any occasion such as a “go to sleep” scene or a “movie night” scene. Give the illusion that someone is home by programming the lights to turn on/off while you are away—perfect for deterring crime and adding additional security!"
</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3030" name="Identifier" type="5250">45604 / ZW4201</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="03 May 2019" revision="1">Initial Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/655/xml</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
  </MetaData>
  <CommandClass id="112"/>
</Product>
