<Product Revision="6" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/0063:3533:5257</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/ge/relay.png</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3533" name="ZWProductPage" type="5257">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/845/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPage">www.ezzwave.com</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Description">"Transform any home into a smart home with the Jasco Z-Wave Wireless Lighting Control Dimmer Switch. The Jasco Z-Wave Wireless Lighting Control Dimmer Switch enables wireless control of on/off and dim functions of hard-wired CFL/LED and Incandescent lighting. The dimmer switch replaces your current light switch, uses your existing wiring, and provides Z-Wave wireless and in-wall control of overhead lighting. Use the dimmer feature to customize the lighting output and create the perfect ambiance for any room. Providing ultimate flexibility, the Jasco Z-Wave Wireless Lighting Control Dimmer Switch allows you to operate the switch by itself or easily integrate the switch with two-way, three-way or four-way wiring configurations by adding the Jasco Auxiliary switch for Z-Wave. Two-way wiring configuration turns the light or appliance on/off from one location. Three-way wiring configuration turns the light or appliance on/off from two separate locations. Four-way wiring configuration turns the light or appliance on/off from three separate locations. The Jasco Auxiliary Switch for Z-Wave is required for three-way or four-way installations.  The dimmer switch includes an LED indicator light to easily locate the switch in a dark room. Take control of your home lighting with Jasco Z-Wave Wireless Lighting Controls!

Z-Wave is the world’s largest ecosystem of interoperable smart home products. Z-Wave lighting controls provide an easy-to-install and affordable system to control lighting and small appliances in your home. Add Jasco Z-Wave lighting controls to a Z-Wave certified gateway to access and control your home from anywhere in the world using your smartphone, tablet or computer as a home automation command center. Never worry if you accidentally left the lights on because you can turn them off remotely or program your lights to go on/off at specific times. Create customized lighting scenes for any occasion such as a “go to sleep” scene or a “movie night” scene. Give the illusion that someone is home by programming the lights to turn on/off while you are away—perfect for deterring crime and adding additional security!"
</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductSupport">http://www.jascoproducts.com/support/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3533" name="Identifier" type="5257">45760/ZW4003</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">In-Wall Toggle Style ON/OFF Relay Switch, Neutral Required, Almond</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="3533" name="FrequencyName" type="5257">U.S. / Canada / Mexico</MetaDataItem>
    <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="03 May 2019" revision="3">Initial Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/653/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="03 May 2019" revision="4">Updated Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/725/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="03 May 2019" revision="5">Updated Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/841/xml</Entry>
      <Entry author="Justin Hammond - Justin@dynam.ac" date="03 May 2019" revision="6">Updated Metadata Import from Z-Wave Alliance Database - https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/845/xml</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
  </MetaData>
  <!-- Configuration Parameters -->
  <CommandClass id="112">
    <Value genre="config" index="3" label="LED Light" max="2" min="0" size="1" type="list" value="0">
      <Help>Sets when the LED on the switch is lit.</Help>
      <Item label="LED on when light off" value="0"/>
      <Item label="LED on when light on" value="1"/>
      <Item label="LED always off" value="2"/>
    </Value>
    <Value genre="config" index="4" label="Invert Switch" size="1" type="list" value="0">
      <Help>Change the top of the switch to OFF and the bottom of the switch to ON.</Help>
      <Item label="No" value="0"/>
      <Item label="Yes" value="1"/>
    </Value>
  </CommandClass>
</Product>
