<Product Revision="1" xmlns="https://github.com/OpenZWave/open-zwave">
  <MetaData>
    <MetaDataItem name="OzwInfoPage">http://www.openzwave.com/device-database/010f:2000:1401</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductPic">images/fibaro/fgwpb121.jpg</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="2000" name="ZWProductPage" type="1401">https://products.z-wavealliance.org/products/2622/</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ExclusionDescription">To remove the device from the Z-Wave network:
1. Plug the device into a socket nearby the main Z-Wave controller.
2. The LED frame will glow green signaling being added (removing
is not necessary otherwise).
3. Set the main controller into remove mode (see the controller’s
manual).
4. Quickly, triple click the button located on the casing.
5. Wait for the removing process to end.
6. Successful 
</MetaDataItem>
<MetaDataItem name="Description">FIBARO Wall Plug is a remotely controlled plug-in switch with the ability to measure power and energy consumption. It uses a LED frame to visualize the current load and operating mode with color changing illumination. FIBARO Wall Plug makes it possible to control electrical devices in a convenient and maintenance-free way. It is also equipped with a USB charging port with power metering.</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ProductManual">https://manuals.fibaro.com/content/manuals/en/FGWPB-121/FGWPB-121-EN-T-v1.0.pdf</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="InclusionDescription">To add the device to the Z-Wave network:
1. Plug the device into a socket nearby the main Z-Wave controller.
2. The LED frame will glow red signaling not being added (reset or
remove the device otherwise).
3. Set the main controller in (Security/non-Security Mode) add mode
(see the controller’s manual).
4. Quickly, triple click the button located on the casing
5. If you are adding in S2 authenticated mode, type in the device pin
code (underlined part of the public key available on the device or
in the manual).
6. Wait for the adding process to end.
7. Successful adding will be confirmed by the Z-Wave controller’s
message.
</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="ResetDescription">Reset procedure allows to restore the device back to its factory settings, which means all information about the Z-Wave controller and user configuration will be deleted. In order to reset the device:
1. Make sure the device is powered.
2. Press and hold the button.
3. Wait for the LED frame to glow yellow (3rd menu position).
4. Release the button.
5. Click the button once to confirm selection.
6. After few seconds the device will restart with factory settings,
which is signaled with the red frame color.
</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="2000" name="Identifier" type="1401">FGWPM-121</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem name="Name">FIBARO Wall Plug</MetaDataItem>
    <MetaDataItem id="2000" name="FrequencyName" type="1401">U.S. / Canada / Mexico</MetaDataItem>
        <ChangeLog>
      <Entry author="Matt Peterson - matt@peterson.org" date="14 Dec 2020" revision="1">Initial Metadata Import</Entry>
    </ChangeLog>
    <MetaDataItem name="WakeupDescription">The FIBARO Wall Plug is powered with the mains voltage so it is always awake.</MetaDataItem>
  </MetaData>


